Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/gauravnarang-88b330129 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

MySQL

Aerospike

Elasticsearch

Languages

English

Hindi

Honors-Awards

2nd Rank Holder in Deen Dayal Upadhyaya College

4th Rank Holder in University Of Delhi

Paytm Rockstar Award for excellent performance in the team

Paytm Rising Star Award for excellent performance during first six months of career at Paytm Mall

GAURAV NARANG

SDE3 @ Adobe| Ex- Gaana, Paytm, Nagarro Greater Delhi Area

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Spring Boot, Java, Apache Kafka. Strong engineering professional with a Msc focused in Computer Science from DEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF DELHI

Experience

Adobe

SDE3

September 2022 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

Gaana

Software Developer

February 2021 - September 2022 (1 year 8 months)

Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

As part of the API team, responsible for creating well optimised API's which are directly used on the various pages of Gaana App or website. Extensively worked to improve latency of different API's which resulted in overall performance improvement of various sections on the Gaana App.

Paytm

2 years 7 months

Senior Software Engineer August 2019 - February 2021 (1 year 7 months)

Noida Area, India

Software Engineer

August 2018 - July 2019 (1 year)

Noida Area, India

Nagarro

Junior Associate

July 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Gurgaon, India

Education

Department of Computer Science, University of Delhi Msc(Computer science), Computer Science · (2015 - 2017)

Deen Dayal Upadhyaya College

Bsc(h) Computer science, Computer Science · (2012 - 2015)